const adobeAnimate_questions = [
  {
    question: "Is a multimedia authoring and animation software developed by Adobe Inc.",
    answer: "Adobe Animate",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "It is used to create interactive animations, vector graphics, and multimedia content for various platforms.",
    answer: "Adobe Animate",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "Adobe Animate provides a comprehensive set of animation tools, including timeline-based animation, frame-by-frame animation, and the ability to create complex animations through keyframes.",
    answer: "Animation Tools",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "Animate primarily uses vector graphics, allowing for scalable and resolution-independent artwork. This is particularly useful for creating graphics and animations that need to be displayed on various devices with different screen sizes.",
    answer: "Vector Graphics",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "In Architectural Design, What addresses the ability of a system to handle processing and loads effectively?",
    answer: "Scalability and Performance",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "One of the strengths of Adobe Animate is its support for interactivity. You can create interactive content by adding actions and scripting using languages like JavaScript. This makes it a popular choice for creating web- based animations and interactive multimedia content.",
    answer: "Interactivity",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: " Animate supports the creation of content for multiple platforms, including web browsers (HTML5 canvas), mobile devices, and desktop applications. This flexibility makes it suitable for a wide range of projects.",
    answer: "Multi-platform Publishing",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "Animate integrates well with other Adobe Creative Cloud applications, allowing users to import assets from Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop. This seamless integration streamlines the workflow for designers and animators who use multiple Adobe tools.",
    answer: "Integration with Other Adobe Software",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "Animate offers various export options, allowing users to publish their animations in different formats such as HTML5, WebGL, SWF (Flash), and more. This flexibility ensures compatibility with various platforms and devices.",
    answer: "Export Options",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: "While Animate is primarily known for 2D animation, it also includes some features for basic 3D animation, allowing users to create simple 3D effects and animations.",
    answer: "3D Animation",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  },
  {
    question: " Adobe Animate supports responsive design, making it easier to create content that adapts to different screen sizes and orientations.",
    answer: "Responsive Design",
    category: "adobeAnimate"
  }
];

export default adobeAnimate_questions;
